

# SHANA PARKER

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

313.575.7514

Parker.shana.parker@gmail.com GitHub: Shana P

LinkedIn : Shana

#### EDUCATION

Front-End Web Developer Bootcamp Grand Circus Detroit Coding Bootcamp Jan. 2017 - March. 2017

--

Studied Liberal Arts Henry Ford Community College / Cuyahoga Community College, 2010-2012

Projects

Final Project Shop Detroit

More to come

SKILLS

HTML5 /CSS
JavaScript
jQuery
Angular
Node.JS
Git/GitHub
Web Design

#### ABOUT ME

After nine years in Retail Management and Fashion industry, I decided to follow my new passion and make a career change into tech. I am a recent graduate of Grand Circus Detroit's 10-week intensive Front-end boot camp of the January cohort. I am looking to create beautiful web applications, with a team of talented web developers.

### EXPERIENCE

Detroit Hustles Harder, 2015 - 2017 Manager

- Managed a team of 4. Handled daily store operations. As well as employee training.
- Projected and created sales goals for weekly, monthly and yearly based on LY & TY sales data. Created reports to track sales(TY, LY, UPT, and ADS).
- Managed inventory and product updates to store website.
- Visual Merchandisina
- Managed customer service and dissolved customer issues.

## SkinnyTees, 2014-2015 Wholesale Assistant

- Collaborated with a team of 8. Fulfilled store and customer orders and assisted in managing inventory.
- Obtained and managed accounts for clients, contractors, and vendors.
- Scouted bloggers to be connected with company for social media campaigns.
- Handled customer service experience and dissolved customer issues.
- Assisted in preparation for photo shoots & events.